Jeron Anthony Reid

42 Erthig Road Belmont, Port of Spain (868) 498-4379 jeronreid20@gmail.com

Dear Hiring Manager,

I am writing to express my strong interest in joining your team at the Port of Spain location. Given my close to three years' experience in several positions in the customer service sector, I believe that am the perfect candidate, and I would appreciate your consideration for a position at your organization.

Due to my time as a Customer Service Representative I possess outstanding communication and problem solving skills which have allowed me to work efficiently. Furthermore, all my experience as a team member enables me to focus not only on my own accomplishments but to cooperate and work on a shared goal willingly. The work experience that I have obtained thus far has transformed me into a proactive worker who is not afraid to dive into new experiences fearlessly. Not to mention being fluent in Spanish and possessing beginner knowledge of both French and Portuguese.

I am an industrious, open-minded and results focused individual who seeks the opportunity to further develop myself and to add to the current working experience which I possess, while sharing my experience with those around me. Furthermore, I am confident in my abilities to contribute positively to the success of any projects and the objectives of your organization.

Please see attached my resume and should my application be considered, I can be contacted at jeronreid20@gmail.com in order to provide any additional information. Thank You.

Yours respectively, Jeron Anthony Reid

Jeron Anthony Reid

42 Erthig Road Belmont, Port of Spain (868) 498-4379 jeronreid20@gmail.com

SKILLS

I am a results focused individual who possesses exceptional interpersonal and time management skills. In addition, I am fluent in Spanish, computer literate and I understand the important role punctuality and teamwork plays in productivity.

EXPERIENCE

• ETutor Trinidad & Tobago

Part-time Tutor (Spanish)
MARCH 2017 - PRESENT

• Caribbean Tutors Ltd

Part-time Tutor (English, Communication Studies, Spanish) OCTOBER 2016 - PRESENT

• Pierre Academia Education

Part-time Tutor (English, Communication Studies, Spanish)
JANUARY 2016 - NOVEMBER 2016

• Scotiabank T&T Limited

Teller, Retail Banking Representative (Contact Centre)
FEBRUARY 2013 - NOVEMBER 2015

Hello Communications Limited

Customer Service Representative, Acting Supervisor (Trincity Mall Branch)
SEPTEMBER 2012 - FEBRUARY 2013

• Keith Khan Books etc.

Customer Service Representative JUNE 2011 - SEPTEMBER 2011

EDUCATION

• The University of the West Indies STA

*BA in Spanish, minor in Linguistics*SEPTEMBER 2014 - PRESENT

• Degree GPA (Present) - 3.57

• Sixth Form Government School

Caribbean Advanced Proficiency Examination (CAPE)
SEPTEMBER 2012 - JULY 2014

- Communication Studies Two
- Caribbean Studies Four
- Sociology Unit 1 Three
- Sociology Unit 2 Four
- Spanish Unit 1 One
- Spanish Unit 2 Two
- French Unit 1 Three
- French Unit 2 Two

• St. Anthony's College

Caribbean Secondary Education Certificate (CSEC) SEPTEMBER 2005 - JULY 2010

- English A One
- Mathematics Two
- Electronics & Electrical Technology One

- Information Technology Two
- Physics Two
- Spanish One
- French One

• St. Francis Boys' RC

Secondary Entrance Assessment (SEA)
SEPTEMBER 1999 - JULY 2005

AWARDS

- *Most Disciplined Player* at Defence Force Youth Team Awards 2010
- Service Quality Management (SQM) World Class Certified Customer Service Representative for 2015 at Scotiabank Contact Centre Fiscal 2014/2015

ACTIVITIES

- The Spanish Club of the University of the West Indies
 - o Executive Member (Part Time Student Representative) 2015/2016
 - Executive Member (Vice President) 2016/2017
- Spanish Theatre Club Member 2015/2016
- UWI Brazilian Portuguese Club (BRASPO)
 - o Executive Member (Secretary) 2016/2017
- English Language Partner on Italki HK Ltd

LANGUAGES

- Spanish C2
- Portuguese A1
- French A1